Speaker: So, this happened some years ago.
I was nineteen, and that summer I finished with my boyfriend.
I wanted to travel as far away as possible, but I needed to get a job!
I was lucky to find temporary work as a receptionist in California, so I booked my flights with a travel agent.
I was really excited. A few weeks later, just five days before my flight, I checked all my travel documents.
Suddenly I noticed a mistake. My surname on the flight booking was Leanna, L-e-a-n-n-a, not Leanne, L-e-a-n-n-e.
Just one small typo, but a very big mistake, because of course the name on my passport was Leanne, and I was sure that was a problem.
I immediately called the travel agent and asked them to change the name on the ticket.
They weren’t stressed at all, and suggested a solution.
‘Don’t worry. We can cancel your ticket and then book you a new one for the same flight.’
It was expensive, but I decided to do it.
When I arrived at the check-in desk, I showed my passport to the assistant, but my name wasn’t on the flight!
I started to panic. I phoned the travel agent and they discovered it was their mistake.
They talked to the woman at check-in. I waited… and I waited…
Finally, she handed me my boarding pass. I was on the flight!
She even arranged transport for me to get through security quickly, and to my gate.
I was the last person to board the plane, but when I was in my seat I finally started to relax.
At last, I was on the biggest adventure of my life!
And the journey ended well – to my great surprise, when I arrived, my suitcase arrived with me!
An absolute miracle!